Miles Johan Bailey-Braendgaard, Software Engineer/Developer

 $Poole, United\ Kingdom, +447391894290, milesbb101@gmail.com$

Nationality	UK, Denmark (EU), and US				
LINKS	Portfolio, LinkedIn, Github				
PROFILE	Eager graduate with a background in computer science, arts, and engineering who is ready to develop, learn, and become a proactive member of your team.				
	Have experience adapting to new languages, IDE's, and technologies and applying them to cross-disciplinary problems.				
	Technologies I often work with include: JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Node.js, CSS SQL, PostgreSQL, Redux, Three.js, Bootstrap, Git/Github, Vercel, Netlify	, HTML, MongoDB,			
EDUCATION					
Jun 2022 — Dec 2022	Full Stack Web Developer Program, EPICODE/Strive School	Remote			
	 High-intensive highly-rated Full-Stack Development Bootcamp (Formerly known focusing on MERN and PERN stack including: Javascript - ES6+, Reactive and Dynamic Web Programming, DOM interact Promises ReactJS - SPA, State & Prop, Classes, Hooks HTML, CSS (Bootstrap, mobile responsiveness) Redux, Typescript NodeJS, ExpressJS, Rest, Middlewares MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, SQL, Mongoose CRUD CORS, Cloud and Streaming (SaaS, PaaS, IaaS), CSV Cryptography and Authentication, JWT, OAuth Ends late December 2022, able to start work from January 3rd 2023 				
Aug 2019 — Jun 2022	BSc Prosthetics and Orthotics, Jönköping University	Jönköping, Sweden			
	 International Society of Prosthetics and Orthotics (ISPO) Accredited Program Clinical, tech, and research focused including modules on statistics Dissertation on the application, accuracy, and reliability of 3D scanning devices and spatial data processing software in the field 				
Jul 2017	UNIQ Oxford University Summer School	Oxford, UK			
	$ \bullet \text{Official summer school run by the university with specialisation in Engineering and including MATLAB and C++} \\$	l Engineering software			
Sep 2014 — Jul 2018	A-Levels and GCSEs, Poole Grammar School	Poole, UK			
	 3 A-Levels: Maths, Electronics, and German 13 GCSEs: including Maths, Further Maths, Computer Science, and Electronics 				
AWARDS					
Jul 2016	Arkwright Engineering Scholarship				
	 Competitive UK-based scholarship sponsoring school and extra-curricular projects in Engineering, Computing, and Technical Design, including a placement at UK-based defence firm Ultra Electronics. 				
EXPERIENCE					
Nov 2021 — Jan 2022	Intern Prosthetist/Orthotist, Aktiv Ortopedteknik	Lund, Sweden			

• Clinical placement working hands-on with patients and collaborating in multidisciplinary teams within Skåne University-Hosptial.

Oct 2019 — Nov 2019	Intern Prosthetist/	Orthotist, Aktiv Ortoped	lteknik	Malmö, Sweden
	• Worked with Malmö P&O specialties such as custom corsets and braces.			
Aug 2020 — Aug 2021	Writer, EDIT New	rspaper		
		topics such as social issues and a ersity student newspaper.	art for both the physica	l and online editions of the
May 2019 — Dec 2019	Software Develope	r, Culture Hustle		Bournemouth, UK
	 Primarily coded in AIML 2.0, HTML, and JavaScript, developed an AI 'Chatbot' for the company to aid in marketing and customer support and UX. 			
Mar 2019 — Jun 2019	Production Assistant, Culture Hustle		Bournemouth, UK	
		sh artist, creator, and activist Stuaintenance of art studio space.	art Semple in both man	ufacture of commercial art supply
Jun 2015	Software Engineer	ing Work Experience, Sier	nens Traffic Solut	rions Poole
	• Shadowed softwa algorithms in C#		st learning about and d	lesigning junction traffic sorting
SKILLS	 Main languages are JavaScript/TypeScript, but have some experience with C# and Solidity, and would be able to quickly learn and adapt to others languages/frameworks required React.js, Node.js, CSS, HTML, MongoDB, SQL, PostgreSQL, Redux, Three.js, Bootstrap, Git Experience with 3D modelling, scanning, printing, and gait analysis software including Canfit, Paromed, Autodesk, Vxelements, Visual3D, and Qualisys People- and detail-oriented, with experience organising and hosting events, trips, and student support in the Jönköping University Student Union 			
LANGUAGES	English	Native speaker	Danish	Highly proficient
	Swedish	Highly proficient	German	Good working knowledge
HOBBIES	Languages - learning M	andarin; Music - play the bass a	and piano; Hiking- ev	very other weekend;

with Upper Limb Prosthetics.

• Adapted quickly to a new patient records databases and software, gained in-depth experience including